## **Amit Jaggi**

## React Developer

Adaptable and proactive Front-End Web Developer on React with 2 years of experience building and maintaining responsive web applications in independent as well as collaborative environments. Passionate about learning and working on new technologies where I can utilize my skills to help drive the success of the organization.

amitjaggi.official@gmail.com

8420464731

Bangalore, India

linkedin.com/in/amit-jaggi-175781134 in

github.com/amit-jaggi

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# **Software Development Engineer - 1**Bolt.Earth

04/2023 - 02/2024 Bangalore, India

EV Charging Station & Software Solution Company

#### **Closed User Group**

**About:** A feature designed to accommodate for exclusive community of users who can conveniently access charging facilities, enhancing the accessibility and convenience of electric vehicle ownership.

 Encompassed the development using React & Hooks, Material-UI for user-friendly interfaces and executed end-to-end test cases using lest

#### **Revenue Splitting**

**About:** A feature introduced to facilitate the distribution of earnings among hosts and other participants involved in various services or transactions for efficient management and allocation of revenue generated from activities such as monthly charging rentals, bookings, or other collaborative ventures.

 Crafted the development using React & Material-UI for a responsive user experience

#### Junior Front-End Developer Bolt.Earth

06/2022 - 03/2023 Bangalore, India

EV Charging Station & Software Solution Company

#### **Host Payment Details**

**About:** A business platform, where the host is allowed to securely upload their payment information such as account, contact, other details into the system for efficient disbursal of funds and earning, fostering trust and transparency in revenue sharing purposes.

 Applied React, Material-UI & REST API's to create a user-friendly interface for efficiently uploading of host details

#### **Currency Conversion**

**About:** A dynamic functionality to convert and display currency values and symbols ensuring accurate global transactions and up-to-date exchange rates.

 Applied React along with currency conversion library to ensure effective data visualization and user engagement.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Master of Computer Applications**

Meghnad Saha Institute of Technology

2017 - 2020 8.37 GPA, Kolkata, India

## **Bachelor of Computer Applications**

NSHM College of Management & Technology

### 2014 - 2017

6.73 GPA, Kolkata, India

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**



## **PROJECT**

#### **Portfolio**

**About:** A simple website showcases my expertise and creativity in web development with a minimalist design and smooth user experience highlighting my projects and skills, crafted with interactive elements and seamless navigation, reflecting my commitment to clean code and attention to detail.

• Link: https://amitjaggi-portfolio.netlify.app/

#### INTERESTS

Gardening Photography Fitness